[In My Prime]
[Episode 4]
Let's actively respond
to the national call
and promote the re-employment
and entrepreneurship
of laid-off workers
to inject vitality into
China's job market and private economy.
Have you heard?
The entire sixth group,
namely the one Li Dazhu is in,
was called in for a talk.
Really?
That group was rated advanced last year.
Well then, Li Dazhu must have
made a fuss over it, didn't he?
Yeah.
But what do we dare say?
I've heard
that our mine has long been
unable to afford payroll.
It's been patching one hole
by digging another.
The list of laid-off workers
this time mainly
consists of lower-level employees like us.
If both husband and wife work here,
one of them must take early retirement.
Aihua,
why are you so quiet?
Have you figured out a plan already?
I'm only an ordinary citizen.
What good plans could I have?
Laid-off workers get severance pay.
Besides, it's good
to never go down the mine again.
It spares us from fear and worry.
Aihua always takes a positive attitude.
You make it sound like nothing,
Aihua.
But what do you think
people like us can do out there?
We've been miners for over 10 years,
covered in dirt every day.
I think it's actually a good thing
to switch to a decent job.
Fine then.
It is getting
warmer and warmer.
I've got you both
thinner sweaters.
Don't take yours off during PE class.
You'll be in trouble if you catch a cold.
Mom.
is that sweater
my brother's hand-me-down?
I'm not wearing it.
I want a new one.
I unraveled his and knitted one for you.
It's just as good as new,
made with top-quality wool.
I treasured it so much that I didn't knit
gloves with it for your dad.
How can you be so picky?
Mom, you're playing favorites.
I'm an elementary school student now.
If I wear my brother's old sweater,
my classmates will laugh at me.
Fine then.
I'll get you a new one.
You two are impossible.
It's like I owe you both.
Go to sleep.
Get up!
Get up.
Let me check on your face.
How did you get so sunburned?
Get up now.
How did this happen?
This morning, you had your hat
and everything on properly.
How did...
your face get so sunburned?
Did you attend PE class?
I've told your teacher about it.
Why didn't you look after
your little sister?
Look at her face.
How did it get so sunburned?
This is indeed a bit serious.
Maybe you should lose that hair clip
and stop trying
to look pretty in the next few days.
What hair clip?
F-Forget I said anything.
I fell asleep already.
I didn't speak a word.
What hair clip?
Show me.
Will you hand it over or not?
Give it to me now,
or I'll talk to your teacher tomorrow.
Who gave these to you?
Look at these.
A good job by Dongfang,
that dear friend of yours.
What now?
Our daughter didn't put on her hat
s-so as to look pretty.
Her face is all sunburned.
Go take a look.
Seriously,
can you
talk to Dongfang?
Before he buys or gifts us
anything in the future,
he should first ask if it's suited for us.
Will you say it or not?
If you don't, I will.
It's inappropriate for you
to say it to him.
I'll talk to him later.
He's not home today, for he is
working overtime.
Working overtime?
At this hour of the day?
Just some mine business.
Are they discussing
the list of layoffs?
I told you to ask him about it.
Have you asked?
He's in charge of HR. What did he say?
You know
what Dongfang is like.
If I'm really on the list,
talking to him won't be of help.
It's fine.
This is not the end of the world.
At this critical moment,
we had better not offend him.
His family and ours
are like one.
Give him some credit, alright?
Listen to yourself.
You always say his family
and ours are like one.
But you never know what goes on
in one's mind.
Only when something serious happens
will you find out
how much
you truly mean to him.
What gives you this much confidence?
For God's sake.
I took over my dad's job
and started working
at the mine in my teens.
Over these decades,
I've made some contributions, haven't I?
If the higher-ups still have a conscience,
given my seniority,
others should be fired
before I am.
It takes a lot of money to raise our kids.
Our daughter's health supplements
cost a massive fortune.
I really can't imagine
what will happen
to our family if you are laid off.
Mr. Cao.
Qinglian, you busy?
I just made some sprout-stuffed buns.
Here you are.
It's Cao Xin's favorite.
I'll let you in on a secret.
Our entire family enjoys it.
That's great.
Qinglian, look.
I bought a lot of groceries.
Bring Aihua and your kids to our place
for dinner tonight.
I'd hate to put you through trouble.
Is Dongfang not home yet?
No, not yet.
God knows
what's going on at the mine recently.
Dongfang is occupied all the time.
Do you need him for something?
Please come over.
Mr. Cao.
Lately at the mine,
hasn't there been talk about layoffs?
I'm a bit worried.
I'm wondering
if Aihua is on the list
of employees to be laid off.
I understand.
Could you please
ask Dongfang about it?
Qinglian,
don't you know
what Dongfang is like?
He never says a word
about work at home.
He's tight-lipped.
But don't you worry.
Who is Aihua to us?
No matter who gets laid off,
it won't be Aihua.
Let me handle it.
Oh, listen to myself.
Dongfang knows
this matter
better than any of us.
So rest assured.
I'm relieved to hear that.
Just don't worry.
Tonight,
bring the kids and Aihua
over for dinner.
Okay.
My father said
Qinglian came to my place,
asking for a word with me.
She always worries about nothing.
What happened to your mouth?
Nothing, just a canker sore.
Don't you fret.
I haven't got the list yet.
In my opinion...
being laid off is not that serious.
What's the big deal?
After all these years,
I've gotten tired of this place.
I've thought it through.
When the time comes,
I'll go to Guangzhou or Shenzhen
to strive for a huge business.
By the time I come back,
perhaps I'll be
wearing big sunglasses,
and a necklace—
I mean a gold one,
and hold a briefcase in my left arm
and a cell phone in my right hand.
In that case, even you will have to
call me Boss Qi.
I truly look forward to that.
One day in the future,
I'd really love to see
what Boss Qi looks like.
Who was it that
stood on top of the mine and said:
"I am to become the mine director!"
"I am to become the Party secretary!"
Yes, the Party secretary.
However,
you fell even before you finished
those sentences.
You took a big tumble.
Dongfang.
Let me tell you something—
it's not a lie.
I am...
truly...
hoping
to work at the mine
for the rest of my life.
I understand. I do.
I am deeply attached
to the mine emotionally.
Dongfang,
you see,
the mine in Qingwu is so gigantic.
Wasn't it said before
that the mining would last
for three generations?
How come the work's finished so soon?
I know nothing but to mine coal.
I've dedicated all my prime years
to the mine.
You can't just toss me aside
when you feel like it.
Please come in.
Dongfang?
You're still here at this hour.
Do you need something?
Yes.
How much did you drink?
You reek of alcohol.
Not much.
Not very much.
Director,
I heard the mine
is downsizing.
Is Qi Aihua
on the layoff list?
Dongfang,
according to the rules,
I shouldn't tell you about it
before the announcement.
I know. I get that.
I'm just...
trying to tell you something,
Director.
Qi Aihua
is a veteran employee
at the mine.
He has made many,
many contributions to this place.
Besides,
his family is truly in difficulty.
He cannot lose his job.
If you dismiss him
simply for falling asleep,
isn't it just making a fuss
over nothing?
Dongfang.
even the closest relationship
can't be compared to a secure job.
How about you get laid off in his stead?
Cao Si!
I want you to have this.
I don't want it.
Just take it.
How am I so nervous
at the sight of Cao Si?
Let's go.
I'm in a good mood today.
I'll treat you to breakfast.
Great!
Let's go!
Go!
Time for breakfast!
Let's head for it!
Breakfast!
Cao Si! Cao Si!
I'll walk to school with you!
Throw this away for me.
I'm going to be late for this morning's
dance training.
You don't want any
of this tasty food?
It's good. I'm just browsing around.
Okay.
Lingzhi!
-Qinglian.
-You just got off work?
You bought a fish?
Aihua works hard down in the mine.
I thought I'd buy him a fish
for nutrition.
I also bought pig blood for the good
of his lungs.
No wonder
you can be in charge of the household.
I can never be
as optimistic as you are.
A serious matter just happened.
And you're still going to
cook fish and stuff.
You treat your husband so well.
What happened?
You have no idea?
This...
The list
of laid-off mine workers is out.
Your husband Aihua is on it.
Qinglian,
I heard someone complained about him,
s-saying that he caused
major safety hazards,
and
t-that he slept at the mine entrance
several times.
He's been used as a bad example.
Qinglian!
Please let me through.
Let me through!
Come on, make way, please.
Make way!
Let me through.
Excuse me.
[Qi Aihua]
Let me through!
Make way!
Qinglian, Qinglian!
The director isn't here.
Qinglian!
Would you stay out?
Look, the director is busy right now.
Who are you?
She's Qi Aihua's wife.
Qi Aihua is on the layoff list
this time, isn't he?
So, she...
Comrade,
listen,
I know how you must feel.
It breaks my heart too.
Before I was transferred
to the mine,
Aihua and his fellow workers
had been working here
for many years.
It's fair to say
that without them,
Qingwu No. 3 Mine
wouldn't be the way it is now.
However, no breakthrough
without breaking down.
The country needs to develop,
and the coal mining sector must advance.
Shouldn't we, as workers,
act in the nation's
best interests?
Director,
I'm hardly
as noble as you are.
Wait.
We are just ordinary citizens.
The walnuts...
Without this stuff,
how do we live?
You're...
I'm telling you,
we need all of these.
Wait. You...
Why...
What...
The water...
You can live without this,
but we can't.
No, wait.
What kind of person is that?
You already know, huh?
Know what?
You were reported for sleeping
at the mine entrance.
You've been laid off.
Who said that?
And you're asking who said that?
It's known to everyone at the mine.
Who saw you sleep?
Who caught you in the act?
Aihua!
How could you be asleep at this hour?
At the mouth of the pit, too?
No way.
I did it only once.
So who saw you there?
Dongfang.
He promised me
he wouldn't tell anyone.
And you believed him
just because he said so?
He can even desert his family
when he's hungry for power.
Why would he care about you?
Dongfang is not like that.
Then what is he like?
Aren't you forced out
of your post now?
Where are you going?
Dongfang.
Qinglian?
Come on in, take a seat.
Sit.
I'm not going in.
I'll speak right here.
Dongfang, we've been friends for years.
It's said a close neighbor
is better than a distant relative.
Years ago, you saved
Aihua at the mine.
We've always kept
your great kindness in mind.
Try putting yourself in our shoes.
You see
how we treat Qi Shi.
Due to Qishi's health condition,
especially her eyes,
we have to supply her
with plenty of vitamin supplements.
Aihua and I have been constantly
upset and scorned
because of Qi Shi.
But we've never
said a single word
of complaint to you, have we?
Right.
We keep all the grievances
to ourselves.
Now, our family is
in utter adversity.
We're not asking you to give us a hand,
but please don't kick us when we're down.
Qinglian, come on, sit down.
Take a seat and have a nice talk,
shall we?
Qinglian,
stop it.
Go home now.
Dongfang,
everyone at the mine says
it was you who reported me
and caused my dismissal.
I did do wrong by sleeping
during work hours.
But that's a different matter.
You are like a brother to me.
Now, I'd like to know
if you reported me.
Dongfang,
I wouldn't be surprised
if you did report me.
Because I know
you are an upright person.
I understand this is the principle
you stick to in everything you do.
But I am your closest friend.
We are practically brothers.
Ever since you saved me
at the mine,
I've considered you my brother.
Then, your family and mine
swapped children.
In my heart,
I truly think of
our two families as one.
Dongfang.
On today's matter,
if it were me,
I would've protected you
even at the cost of my life,
let alone a job.
That means nothing.
Mom, I'm home!
Mom,
why did you leave the fish
and groceries on the ground?
A desk lamp?
Did you buy it for me and Qi Shi?
A premium tea bottle.
A gourd.
Mom,
why did you buy a gourd?
Fine tea.
Is it for my dad?
Mom,
I've also brought you something nice.
There's a lot of bubble gum in here.
I'm saving it all for Qi Shi.
It's her favorite.
And I got all this stuff
from Cao Si this morning.
Uncle Cao and his family are so nice,
for giving us so many nice things.
Mom,
a piece of White Rabbit Candy for you.
Mom, take it.
Someone caused your father
to lose his job.
And now a few pieces of candy are enough
to silence you.
Mom, Mom!
You think we want
this junk from you?
Qinglian,
just say whatever you have to say.
Why take it out on the child?
I'm educating my child.
It's none of your business.
Stop embarrassing yourself.
Go back into the house.
I'm embarrassing?
How so?
I live an honest and upright life.
A straight tree is not afraid of
crooked shadows.
I'm different from some people
who act like good friends
on the surface
and secretly
stab others in the back.
Cao Dongfang,
let's make it all clear today.
When everything is fine,
you bring chicken soup
and all sorts of things over.
You talk a good game
about us being a family.
But when trouble arrives,
you turn your back on us.
We are so unlucky
to be your neighbors.
What's going on?
-What is this about?
-Qinglian,
what do you mean by that?
What do I mean?
I'd like everyone present
to be a witness.
From now on, the Cao and Qi families
are strangers to each other!
They used to be very close.
Is there a misunderstanding?
The quarrel is so intense.
Yeah.
Can't they clear up the misunderstanding?
Why a fierce fight?
Yeah.\
Never thought she'd be like this.
Go home, all of you!
Look how furious Qinglian is.
Cao Si, don't cry.
It's typical of my mom.
All will be fine in time.
How about dipping it in soy sauce?
I'd like to dip it in sugar.
Easy on the sugar.
Eating too much of it
is bad for your teeth.
I miss Mr. Cao's chicken soup.
What do you think has gotten into Mom?
She was so mad today.
What if Cao Si and Cao Xin
never talk to us anymore?
I also want to have chicken soup.
I already had a plan with Si.
Tonight, she is supposed
to teach me how to dance.
Zhi,
do you think
Uncle Cao is the kind of person
Mom says he is?
I don't know.
How about we sneak to their place?
No, don't.
Mom is still angry.
Don't make things worse.
Dad got laid off.
In the future,
we can't afford coal briquettes,
and not even dry steamed buns.
Let me tell you something.
Today, both parents
of a classmate of mine got laid off.
Their entire family had to return
to their hometown.
They cried miserably
when they left.
Several classmates of mine have
transferred to other schools.
Could it be for the same reason?
Perhaps we'll also have to
reside in the countryside one day.
Then you won't be able to get a wife.
Actually,
Uncle Cao doesn't
strike me as a bad person.
But what Mom said today
isn't entirely wrong.
Dad really did get laid off.
To keep the peace of the family,
we'll have to sever ties
with Cao Si and Cao Xin.
You haven't eaten anything all day.
Grab a bite at least.
About your job,
we'll figure something out.
Have a bite.
It's just a layoff, come on.
It's not like the sky has fallen.
Even if it does,
taller people will hold it up.
You do have some skills.
Good job fixing the brush.
I mean it.
The bristles were all worn out.
I was going to throw it away.
But after being repaired
by you, it looks as good as new.
This could easily
sell for 50 or 80 cents
in the market, right?
You can't get this quality
for 50 or 80 cents.
Two yuan then.
How about this?
Tomorrow, let's set up a stall
in the market
to sell the brushes and shovels
you made.
This stuff you made
is much better than that
in our department store.
We can also buy some daily necessities
and start a small business.
There's always a way out, right?
Come on.
Eat up.
I'll eat.
There is always
a way out.
Dongfang.
Dongfang!
Dad.
I'm thinking about
taking our money out of this bankbook
and giving it to Aihua and his family.
On this matter, we're in the wrong.
Things have gotten so bad
that they won't accept our money.
Forget it.
Si,
will Qi Zhi
and Qi Shi never
talk to us again?
What do you think?
Si, stop crying.
I'm not crying.
Uncle C...
Cao Xin, you're back.
Cao Xin!
Come over.
Wait here for a bit.
Here you are.
You must be hungry, huh?
Do they not feed you enough at home?
Take these home with you.
Don't tell your grandpa
or your dad, though.
Okay.
Wash your hands. Dinner's ready.
Go.
We can solve the problem this way.
Split 360
into two numbers
of 190
and 170.
Then,
170 minus 70
gives a round number,
namely 100, right?
Ma'am,
why isn't the 2 p.m. bus
to Haizhou here?
That bus was full,
so it left early.
When?
About 5 minutes ago.
♪ Countless times I broke the rules ♪
♪ Countless times I longed to break free ♪
♪ I loudly laughed, mocked,
expressed anger, and yelled ♪
♪ Then I realized I missed you dearly ♪
Cao Si! Cao Si!
♪ Countless times I searched for answers ♪
Cao Si!
Did you run here from the bus station?
♪ Would I be better off
if I lived a different life ♪
Cao Si,
why go to the provincial capital?
♪ But it turns out living in one's prime ♪
I'm heading there to learn dancing.
My dad wouldn't let me tell you.
♪ Just means ♪
The provincial city is great.
♪ That we can set out together ♪
When will you be back then?
I'm not sure yet.
When you get there,
write to me, will you?
I'll be waiting.
Okay.
♪ An old sofa ♪
Do remember to write to me.
The bus is leaving.
♪ A group photo
and several pots of flowers ♪
Head back inside.
Don't forget what I said.
♪ A few words of everyday talk ♪
Do remember to write to me!
♪ I wish time could stop right now ♪
Cao Si,
don't forget to write to me!
Goodbye, Cao Si!
♪ The revolving winters and summers ♪
Goodbye!
♪ I grew up in the midst of chaos ♪
Cao Si!
♪ The world is full of changes ♪
Bye bye!
♪ With the door closed,
I'm back to the old days ♪
That kid is
quite a good runner.
♪ Countless times I broke the rules ♪
He's a natural athlete.
♪ Countless times I longed to break free ♪
♪ I loudly laughed, mocked,
expressed anger, and yelled ♪
♪ Then I realized I missed you dearly ♪
♪ Countless times I searched for answers ♪
Hey,
here's chicken soup.
I happen to be thirsty.
♪ Would I be better off
if I lived a different life ♪
Slow down. Or you'll choke.
♪ But it turns out living in one's prime ♪
Later on,
have Qi Shi come here.
♪ Just means ♪
This bowl is for her.
♪ That we can set out together ♪
Forget it. Qi Shi won't drink it.
She'll even tattletale to my mom.
It's better to stay out of trouble.
I'll have this bowl too.
[The 6th-grade final exam results
of Qingwu Central Elementary School]
[No. 1: Cao Xin]
[No. 2: Qi Shi]
[The 7th-grade final exam ranking
of Qingwu Middle School]
[No. 1: Cao Xin]
[No. 2: Qi Shi]
[The 9th-grade final exam ranking
of Qingwu Middle School]
[No. 1: Qi Shi]
[No. 2: Cao Xin]
[The 11th-grade monthly exam ranking
of Qingwu High School]
[No. 1: Cao Xin]
[No. 2: Qi Shi]
Pack five buns for me.
Sure.
All with vegetable fillings?
I'd like two as well.
Qinglian!
It's been a while
since I last saw you.
Yeah. Buying buns?
How about I get you two?
No need.
I've had breakfast.
The buns look pretty nice.
You're carrying many bags.
You bought so much food.
My son's coming home tonight.
That explains it.
You're so lucky.
Of your two children,
one always ranks first in exams,
and the other got into
the provincial sports school.
You don't have to
worry about them at all.
You haven't aged a bit all these years.
Easy for you to say.
You guys just never saw
the hard times I went through.
I did.
It's all fine
now that you've made it through.
Your daughter, Qi Shi,
will probably
be the top scorer
in the college entrance exam.
And your son, Qi Zhi,
might win an Olympic gold medal.
Then your family will move up
in the world.
From your lips to God's ears.
I'll host a big banquet if that happens.
I'll be waiting then.
Okay.
Qinglian, a look at the clothes?
This jacket seems good.
Qinglian.
Do you remember
the department store
we used to work at?
It's been torn down.
I went for a visit.
There stands a commercial building now.
It's so grand.
The clothes in there... How...
How much is this?
Ninety yuan.
-That expensive?
-Ninety?
This is made for export.
We'll browse around.
At that place,
a random piece of clothing costs
over a hundred.
How expensive.
Those days of easy living
are gone now.
Everyone has to rely on themselves.
Your husband Aihua is an exception.
He seized the opportunity
and got a stall here. How very nice.
But my husband,
can't do this at all.
The entire household depends on him.
We're all the same, struggling to get by.
Alright. I'm leaving then.
Okay.
I have to mind the stall now.
That earpick seems good.
Why not throw one in for free?
I've bought so many things from you.
Just throw in a free gift.
Fine.
Since you're a regular,
a free earpick for you.
Okay. Good.
Does this fan work well?
It does.
It's a palm-leaf fan.
How about this?
Let me take it home and try it out.
I'll pay you tomorrow.
Okay.
Hold on!
Th-This...
You...
Which of these things did he pay for?
I bought this.
Which one did he pay for?
The soap.
Wait.
Didn't he say it was free of charge?
Penny wise, pound foolish.
Do you know?
How could you do business this way?
This is exactly the way I do business.
Will you leave or not?
It...
He only bought one bar of soap.
Why not give him everything at our home?
At this rate, our business
will eventually go south.
Don't you think our family is poor
enough?
Alright, let's go home
i-if you don't want to run the stall.
Our son's coming home tonight.
Okay. I'll pack up then.
Mr. Cao.
Mr. Cao!
Look at your chicken.
Instead of staying in your own yard,
it constantly comes to my place
and ruins my vegetables.
Why don't you
just give it to me?
I'll either stew it
or braise it.
You see...
Listen to yourself.
Don't be so mean.
It's just a little chicken.
Why get mad at it at all?
Fine, you can have it.
But do you know how to cook it?
Your daughter's in her second year
of high school now.
She needs plenty of nutrition.
She's my own daughter.
I know how to take care of her.
I don't need your tutoring.
I know. I get it.
Mom, Mom.
It h-hurts.
I'm having a cramp again.
A-A cramp?
Did you run back here?
How many times have I told you
to take a bus?
We can afford the fees.
It hurts. It really hurts. Give me a hand.
It's dusty here near the mine.
Look at your neck, covered
in dust due to all that running.
Mom, help me. Mom.
It really hurts a lot.
The chicken!
I'm in so much pain, Mom.
We are already home.
Hang in there.
Come on. Come home with me.
Don't you wander off again.
Let's go home.
Dinner's ready.
There are two grown men in the house,
yet neither of you offers to serve.
All the chores at home are mine.
Don't fight me for it.
Dad, let me do it.
I rarely come home.
I will do it. I will.
You two
drop the act now.
Neither of you can be counted on.
I'll serve the food myself.
Look at the fish your mom cooked.
It smells so good.
Take a sniff.
Am I right?
Yes.
The only thing missing is cilantro, right?
I'll go pluck some.
Taking a stroll, aren't you?
Grandpa,
I'm back.
Taking a stroll, huh?
Are you going to work?
I am already off work.
How do you know
I love walnut cookies?
Of course I do.
Let's go.
Come in and take a seat.
It's from the factory.
I'm done exercising.
Let me get some water.
Got it, Dad.
He's confused again.
And you squandered money again.
You don't earn much.
How can you be a squanderer?
I just bought these on my way home.
Don't you enjoy
walnut cookies?
That doesn't mean
you get to squander money.
There's no cilantro here.
In that case,
go out to buy some!
Stop taking things from others
all the time.
Or they'll whine about it.
Mom, I'm going out to buy cilantro now.
Si!
Come here.
Dad.
Mom, I bought cilantro.
Don't you say I'm a martial arts champion?
I practice running, so I run fast.
Wash it up and chop it.
Okay.
Come back!
What is it, honey?
Tell Qi Shi to come have dinner.
Okay.
Sweetie,
time for dinner!
Coming right up.
She does zero chores all day long
and never comes to eat
when it's meal time.
Shi would love to do chores,
but you won't let her.
You think we're so rich that she gets
to ruin everything?
She drops a plate
every time she carries one.
Dad,
keep spoiling him
and sparing him from chores.
He has to study.
That matters most.
College boy, come out for dinner.
Don't distract him.
Cao Xin, come here.
Come on.
Take these to your room. Eat them.
Grab a few bites.
I'll go buy some more food.
But...
Get back to your studies.
Dad,
stop pushing him.
His grades are great now.
I'm sure he can get into a college.
Not only does he have to go to college,
but he also has to study a good major
in a good college.
In the future,
he'll have to apply for graduate school
and become a useful person to the society.
Grandpa,
let's have dinner first.
Careful.
Aren't we having walnut cookies?
Dad gave them all to Cao Xin.
Go get chopsticks.
Our family has
a martial arts champion
and a literary champion.
I say, Sweetie,
work hard on your studies.
By getting into Beining University,
you'll bring honor to me
and your mom.
Whether I can get into
Beining University aside,
I am sure I will do
better than Cao Xin in the exam,
who lives next door.
Right.
I won't force you to get into
college.
Most importantly,
you must master a skill
so you can support yourself.
Here,
have some fish.
I already picked out
the bones for you.
Some shredded potatoes for you.
Thanks, Zhi.
Your mom's cooking is really good.
Right?
Am I right?
Yes, so tasty.